p2sample.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy - Global Online Sample Provider & Market Research Panel | P2Sample

**PRIVACY POLICY**

 **Last updated 05/23/2018** **  
** **  
** **Overview**

This document establishes the privacy policies of P2Sample.com websites as well as its compliance with specific national and international jurisdictions (including the privacy regulations and laws thereof). The publication of this document rescinds all previous privacy policies – implied, spoken or written.

 **Organization Information**

The principal activities of P2Sample.com are market research.

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of P2Sample.com. P2Sample is based in United States and at the following postal address:

3159 Royal Drive, Suite 360  
Alpharetta, GA, 30022  
United States of America

P2Sample can be reached via e-mail at [info@P2Sample.com](mailto:info@P2Sample.com)

 **Anonymous Access**

Visitors can access the website/application home pages and browse sites/applications without disclosing personal data.

 **Services and Links**

P2Sample.com sites and applications may include links to third-party web/mobile service providers. P2Sample.com is not responsible for the content, accuracy, or privacy policies of third-party web/mobile services.

 **Data collection**

We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on P2Sample.com includes:

Personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number, that you voluntarily give to us on the contact form on P2Sample.com, while signing up for the newsletter or upon downloading documents on P2Sample.com. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however, your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of P2Sample.com and our mobile application.  

 **** **Automatic Data Collection**

P2Sample.com may collect information from your computer, mobile phone or other access devices. The information sent to us includes, but is not limited to, data on the pages you access, your computer IP address, referral data, device identifiers, the type of operating system you’re using, your location (GPS), mobile network information, standard web log data and other information. Weblog data includes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from our site to determine trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

 **Data Collection and Purpose**

P2Sample respects your privacy.

Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via P2Sample.com or our mobile application to:  

  * Fulfill download requests executed on P2Sample.com
  * Send you a newsletter.  
  * Request feedback about P2Sample.com
  * Notify you of updates to P2Sample.com
  * Offer new products, services, mobile applications, and/or recommendations to you
  * Perform other business activities as needed
  * Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoenas.
  * Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties

Access to collected personal data is available upon request.

 **Sharing and Cookies**

P2Sample uses cookies to provide a better user experience. Find more information on <https://www.p2sample.com/cookie-policy/>

**Children's Privacy**

P2Sample.com does not knowingly collect personal data from individuals under the age of 16. Minors 16 to 18 are permitted to access the services of the site only with parental permission. It is the responsibility of the individual and the parent to ensure such permissions are obtained. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 16. If we are notified of this and as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers.

 **Disclosure**

We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows:   
  
**By Law or to Protect Rights**

If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation.  This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 **Third-Party Service Providers**

We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance.  

 **Sale or Bankruptcy**

If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity.  If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy.

We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control third-party solicitations. If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.

 **Confidentiality and Security**

P2Sample.com has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

P2Sample.com employees and data processors with access or association to the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of visitor personal data.

P2Sample.com does not disclose personal data to State institutions and authorities unless required by law.

 **Access to Personal Data**

You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account  by sending an email to [info@P2Sample.com](mailto:info@P2Sample.com)

Access to personal information may require proof of identity. Access to personal data is provided without charge. Personal data may be challenged or updated and, where appropriate, data will be completed, erased, rectified or amended. 

**Emails and Communications**

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by:  

  * Clicking the unsubscribe button in emails

 **CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Site or our mobile application, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Site or our mobile application. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California.  We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Site or our mobile application, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.

 **CONTACT US**

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

P2Sample  
3159 Royal Drive, Ste 360,  
Alpharetta, GA 30022

Phone: (404) 446 - 2720
